Juan Sebastián Bravo Santacruz

<u>LinkedIn | GitHub</u> Email: <u>bravos.js@javeriana.edu.co</u> | Mobile: +57 3212815679

ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING STUDENT

Last semester student of Electronics Engineering with a keen interest in **machine learning**, **signal processing**, **bioengineering**, and **computer vision**. My biggest passion now lies in **neuroengineering**, especially **neuroimaging** and **Signal Processing**. I have experience working with Python modules such as TensorFlow, scikit-learn, and PyTorch, along with knowledge of machine learning algorithms and deep learning.

EDUCATION

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana

Bogotá, Colombia Jul 2018 – Sept 2023

Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering

GPA : 4.57/5.00 — Nine Academic Excellence Awards.

Relevant Courses: Artificial Intelligence (4.8/5.0), Image Processing and Computer Vision (5.0/5.0), Signal Processing

(4.8/5.0), Continuous Time Signals (4.9/5.0), Discrete Time Signals (5.0/5.0).

EXPERIENCE

Big Data & Analytics Intern

Jan 2023 – Jul 2023 Bogotá, Colombia

Accenture

- Assistance in the development of proof of concept (**PoC**) chat bot using **generative AI** and **LLM** on **Azure**. Use of FormRecognizer, Azure Functions, and OpenAI suite.
- Design of scripts for the implementation of **ETLs** in **Databricks**, using technologies such as **SQL** and **PySpark**. Use of **daltalakes** and **data warehouse**.
- Support and monitoring of infrastructure deployed in the **AWS** cloud.
- Development of infrastructure as code IaC using terraform on architecture deployed in the AWS cloud.

Teacher Assistant

Aug 2020 – Dec 2022 Bogotá, Colombia

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana

- Teacher assistant of the subject Continuous Time Signals.
- Teacher assistant of the subject Signals and Systems.

PROJECTS

Thesis: Multimodal system to assist in the diagnosis of Mild Cognitive Impairment from MRI Images Source Code

- Classification of volumetric MRI images of the brain using **deep learning** (Resnet-50) and **machine learning** (Tested the following algorithms: XGBoost, SVM, Logistic Discriminant, Random Forest, Dense Neural Networks).
- Multimodal system (based on a regression model and MLP) involving MRI images classification and cognitive test
 results, for giving a probability of having MCI.
- Use of Bayesian Optimization algorithm for hyper-parameters tuning of machine learning models.
- Design of User interface involving image importing, image visualization (before and after skull stripping) and the diagnosis. App was hosted at huggingface.

Skull Stripping from MRI Images using 3D U-Net

Source Code

- Preprocessing of volumetric MRI images of the brain (Filtering, normalization, resizing).
- Training of a 3D U-Net network using Keras for semantic segmentation of brain in volumetric MRI images.

AF Classification from a single lead of ECG recording using machine learning

Source Code

- Preprocessing of ECG signals (**Filtering**, QRST cycle detection, **feature extraction**).
- Training of a **deep neural network** (DNN) for classifying ECG recordings as Atrial Fibrillation or Normal Control patients.

LANGUAGES

Spanish : Native

English : Certified C1, IELTS score: 7.5

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming : Python, MATLAB, C, SQL

Libraries : Pytorch, Tensorflow, scikit-learn, Keras, Pandas, Numpy, OpenCV, SciPy, Matplotlib

Tools : Git, Databricks, Jupyter Notebooks, Google Colaboratory

Clouds : AWS (Basic), Azure (Basic)

CERTIFICATIONS

• CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python — HarvardX